A Guide to the Directors' Correspondence of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1933-1977 (bulk 1934-1976)
Library of Virginia
- Membership Committee, 1947-1956 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Membership Committee 1972 September 11, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Membership Committee: Meeting 1957 October 29, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 35)
- Membership Committee: Meeting 1972, October 12, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Membership Committee: Minutes, 1954-1956 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Membership Committee: Report, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Membership Drive, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Membership Drive, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Membership Information, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Membership Letters, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Membership Letters, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Membership Mailing, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Membership Mailings, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Membership Possibilities, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Membership Solicitation Proposals, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Membership Survey, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Membership: Corporate, 1950-1957 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Membership: Corporate, 1950-1957 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Membership: Corporate, 1960-1962 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Membership: Corporate, Plans, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Memos: Fall Lecture Series, 1954-1955 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Memos: General, 1949-1952 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Memos: General, 1949-1952 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 34)
- Memos: General, 1952-1954, folder 1 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Memos: General, 1952-1954, folder 2 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Memos: General, 1952-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 35)
- Memos: General, 1953-1954, folder 1 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Memos: General, 1953-1954, folder 2 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Memos: General, 1953-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 36)
- Memos: General, 1954-1957 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Memos: General, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Memos: General, 1956 January - June, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Memos: General 1956 January - June, 1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 37)
- Memos: General, 1956 July - December, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Memos: General 1956 July - December 1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 38)
- Memos: General, 1956-1958, folder 1 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Memos: General, 1956-1958, folder 2 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Memos: General, 1956-1958 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 39)
- Memos: General, 1957-1958 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Memos: General, 1958 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 40)
- Memos: General, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Memos to the Staff, 1949-1951 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Mental Health in Virginia, 1951-1954 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1955-1956 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1959-1963 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1959-1963 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 41)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1968-1976 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Michel Jacobs Gallery, 1934-1936 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Michel Jacobs Gallery, 1934-1936 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 42)
- Midwestern Books Competition, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Mielziner, Jo, 1950-1953 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Mielziner, Jo, 1954-1966 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Mielziner, Jo, 1954-1966 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 43)
- Miller and Rhodes, Inc., 1949-1953 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Miller and Rhodes, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Miller and Rhodes Forum, 1960 November, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Miller, John M., Jr., 1935-1943 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Milliken, William, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Milliken, William, 1958-1959 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 44)
- Mills, Berry, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Mint Museum of Art, 1946-1953 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Mint Museum of Art, 1946-1953 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 45)
- Miscellaneous, undated (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Moby Dick: Gil Wilson, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Modern German Art, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Monroe Memorial Foundation, 1957-1960 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Monument Avenue Commission, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Monument Avenue Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Moore, Charles, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Moore, Merrill, 1952-1957 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Moore, Merrill, 1952-1957 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Morgan, Georgia, 1935-1945 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Morris, Emma: Photographs, undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Morrison, William W., 1959-1965 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Movies: Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Mullholland, John, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Mumford, Louis, 1955-1958 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Munn, Margaret Crosby Estate, 1946-1949 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Munn, Margaret Crosby Estate, 1946-1949 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 46)
- Mural: Virginia State Library, 1946-1950 (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Mural: Virginia State Library, 1946-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 47)
- Museo Nacional de Mexico: Photographs and Negatives, undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Museum Attendance Record, 1967-1971 (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Museum Bulletin, 1942-1949 (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Museum Bulletin: 1954 October, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Museum Bulletin: 1955 October, 1955 [1] (Box 43, Folder 38)
- Museum Bulletin: 1955 October, 1955 [2] (Box 43, Folder 39)
- Museum Christmas Cards, 1948-1956 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Museum Entertainment: 1967/68 and 1968/69 Seasons, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Museum Guests, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Museum Information, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Museum Information: Miscellaneous, 1946-1956 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Museum Information: Miscellaneous, 1946-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 48)
- Museum Maintenance, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Museum Methods Program 1972 January 4, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Museum Motion Picture, 1946-1948 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Museum Notes, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Museum Notices, 1955-1956 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Museum of Modern Art, 1954-1963 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Museum of Modern Art, 1969-1975 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Museum Operations, 1940-1956 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Museum Operations, 1940-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 49)
- Museum Operations, 1955-1956 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Museum Photographs, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Museum Planting, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Museum Policy, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Museum Printing, 1944-1947 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Museum Promotion, 1949-1956 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Museum Promotion, 1955-1956 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Museum Reorganization, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Museum Schedule, 1966-1971 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Museum Schedule, 1970-1972 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Museum Schedule, 1971-1973 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Museum Speeches, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Museum Store, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Museum Tours, 1947-1956 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Museum Tours, 1966-1970 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Museum Tours, 1966-1970 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Museum Tours: Requests, General, 1950-1954 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Museums: General, 1946-1967 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Museums: General, 1946-1967 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 50)
- Museums: General, 1970-1976 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Museums: General, 1972-1975 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Museums: General, 1972-1975 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 51)
- Museums: General, 1972-1975 (SLIDES) (Box 89, Folder 11-12)
- Museums and Galleries: General, 1959-1966 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Museums and Galleries: General, 1959-1966 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 52)
- Music Committee, 1952-1954 (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Music Programs (Recorded) 1944-1945, 1944-1946 (Box 44, Folder 35)
- Myers, Joseph, 1936-1949 (Box 44, Folder 36)
- N: General, 1934-1940 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- N: General, 1950-1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- N: General, 1950-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 53)
- N: General, 1967-1970 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- N: General, 1972-1976 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- N: General, 1972-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 54)
- Namuth, Hans, 1961-1963 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Namuth, Hans, 1961-1963 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 55)
- National Council for the Arts, 1960-1972 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- National Council for the Arts, 1960-1972 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 10)
- National Council on the Arts, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- National Cultural Center, 1959-1961 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- National Cultural Center, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- National Cultural Center, 1962-1963 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 11)
- National Education Association: Dept. of Audiovisual Instruction, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- National Endowment for the Arts 1966/67, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- National Endowment for the Arts, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- National Endowment for the Arts, 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- National Endowment for the Arts, 1973-1975 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 56)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Chamber Music Audience Development Program, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- National Endowment for the Arts: General Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Prior to Approval, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Prior to Approval, 1965-1966 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 57)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Proposals, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Traveling Theatre, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- National Endowment Fund: Visual Arts, James Browne, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- National Exhibition: Designer Craftsmen 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- National Gallery of Art, 1935-1944 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- National Gallery of Art, 1935-1944 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 58)
- National Gallery of Art, 1965-1976 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- National Park Recreation Week, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1956-1966 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Native Art of the Northwest Pacific Coast, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Native Art of the Northwest Pacific Coast, 1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Naval Review (June 12, 1957), 1957 (Box 90, Folder 36)
- Near, Pinkney, 1960-1961 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Near, Pinkney, 1969-1971 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Near, Pinkney, 1969-1971 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 59)
- Near, Pinkney, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Near, Pinkney, 1974-1975 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 60)
- Near, Pinkney, 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Near, Pinkney, 1975-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 61)
- New Museum Hours, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- New York Cocktail Party, 1952-1955 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Newsletter (Virginia Art Alliance), 1936 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Newsletter Material, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Newsom, Earl and Co., 1958-1960 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Newsom, Earl and Co.: Report, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Newsom Program: 25th Anniversary Campaign Second Mailing 1959 October, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Newsom Program: 25th Anniversary Fund Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Nicholas, Donald, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Nicholas, Donald, 1970-1971 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 62)
- Nicholas, Donald, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Nicholas, Donald, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Nicholas, Donald, 1974-1975 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 63)
- Nicholas, Donald, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Nichols, Fred, 1963-1967 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Nicholson, James V., 1955-1957 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Norton Simon Collection, 1970-1973 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Nottingham, Elizabeth (WPA Project), 1935-1937 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Nystad, Saam, 1962-1967 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Nystad, Saam, 1962-1967 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 64)
- O: General, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- O: General, 1957-1972 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- O: General, 1957-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 65)
- O: General, 1973-1976 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- O: Miscellaneous, 1940-1953 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- O'Neal, William B., 1961-1963 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Occidental Painting: Traveling Exhibition #9, undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Oenslager, Donald, 1950-1969 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Oenslager, Donald, 1950-1969 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 66)
- Old Dominion Foundation, 1954-1961 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Old Dominion Foundation, 1957-1967 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Olney, Dan, 1940-1943 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- One-Man Show Possibilities, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Open House, undated (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Opening: 1954 October 29 Governors, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Opening: 1954 October 29 Receiving Line, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Opening: Members' Suite, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Opera Society of Washington, Inc., 1957 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- Operations: Printing, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Operations: Receptionist, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 36)
- Operations: Refreshment Room, 1955-1956 (Box 46, Folder 37)
- Operations: Theatre, 1955-1956 (Box 46, Folder 38)
- Organization Chart, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 39)
- Organization Lists, 1953-1956 (Box 46, Folder 40)
- Orloff, Nicholas, 1949-1950 (Box 46, Folder 41)
- Ornament, 1954-1955 (Box 46, Folder 42)
- Other Museums, 1955-1956 (Box 46, Folder 43)
- P: General, 1934-1939 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- P: General, 1934-1939 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 13)
- P: General, 1965-1972, folder 1 of 2 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- P: General, 1965-1972, folder 2 of 2 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- P: General, 1972-1976 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- P: General, 1972-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 67)
- Painter, Sidney, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Parker, T. Nelson, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Parking Area Controversy, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Parsons, Mrs. James, 1960-1966 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Patron of Arts, 1936-1937 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Payne, John Barton, Library Exchange, 1938-1950 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania, University of, 1959-1965 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- People-to-People Program, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Periodicals: Art News, 1952-1964 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Periodicals: Articles, 1966-1972 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Periodicals: Commonwealth Magazine, 1947-1960 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Periodicals: Commonwealth Magazine, 1956-1960 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Periodicals: General, 1965-1970 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Periodicals: General, 1965-1970 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Periodicals: General, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Periodicals: New York Times, 1963-1970 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Periodicals: Richmond Newspapers, 1957-1965 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Periodicals: Time Magazine, 1960-1964 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Periodicals: Time-Life, 1964-1969 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Personnel: Curator, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Personnel: Employees, 1954-1956 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Personnel: Employees, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Personnel: General, 1937-1953 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Personnel: General, 1954-1956 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Personnel: General, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Personnel: General, 1966-1970 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Personnel: General, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Personnel: Grounds Supervisor, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Personnel: Handbook, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Personnel: Merit Ratings, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Personnel: Public Information Director, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Personnel: Public Relations - Friddell, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Personnel: Restorer Position, 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- Personnel: State Personnel Rules, 1946, folder 1 of 2 (Box 47, Folder 36)
- Personnel: State Personnel Rules, 1946, folder 2 of 2 (Box 47, Folder 37)
- Personnel: State Staff Survey, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Personnel: State Staff Survey - Responses, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Peyton, Mrs. Philip, 1937-1939 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1935-1945 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1935-1945 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 68)
- Philanthropic Giving, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Phillips, E. Turpin, Jr., 1954 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Phillips, John G., 1971-1973 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Phillips Memorial Gallery, 1935-1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Phillips Memorial Gallery, 1935-1936 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 69)
- Photo Purchase Requests, 1945-1956, folder 1 of 3 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Photo Purchase Requests, 1945-1956, folder 2 of 3 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Photo Purchase Requests, 1945-1956, folder 3 of 3 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Photo Purchase Requests, 1951-1952 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Photo Purchase Requests, 1952-1956 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Photo Purchase Requests, 1954-1956 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Photographer, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Photographic Salon: 19th, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Photographs, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Photographs removed from file, 1952-1956 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Photography in the Fine Arts, 1959-1968 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Piccirilli, Attilio, 1935-1944 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Pictura, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Pictura Films Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Poetry Society of Virginia, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Policy Operation, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Pollard, John Garland, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Pollard, John Garland, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Pollard, John Garland, 1936 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 70)
- Pollard, John Garland, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- Pollard, John Garland, Jr., 1953-1961 (Box 48, Folder 28)
- Pollard, John Garland, Jr., 1964-1968 (Box 48, Folder 29)
- Pollard, Mrs. John Garland, 1949-1955 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Pollard, Mrs. John Garland, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Pollard, Mrs. John Garland, Sr.: Membership and Business, 1954-1960 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Pomodoro, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Pomodoro, 1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 71)
- Porterfield, Robert, 1967-1970 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Portraits by David Payne, 1951-1953 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Portraits by David Payne, 1951-1953 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 72)
- Portraits, Inc., 1945-1953 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Powell, John, Foundation, 1951 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Pratt, John Lee, 1939-1954 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Pratt, John Lee, 1939-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 73)
- Pratt, John Lee, 1949-1959 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Pratt, John Lee, 1951-1955 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Pratt, John Lee, 1957-1972 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Pratt, John Lee, 1957-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 74)
- Pratt Catalogue, 1950-1956 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Pratt Collection, 1947-1950 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Pratt Collection, 1947-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 75)
- Pratt Collection, 1949-1955 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Pratt Collection, 1949-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 76)
- President's Letter, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Press Releases - October, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Press Releases - October, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Preview Arrangements, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Price, Governor James H., 1938-1941 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Price, Vincent, 1963-1970 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Priest, Alan, 1961-1969 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Priest, Alan, 1961-1969 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 77)
- Priest, Alan, 1967-1969 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Printing, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Printing: Guide Sheets for Schools, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Printing: Layouts, 1948-1949 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Printing: Layouts, 1948-1949 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 16)
- Printing: Samples (Museum), 1946-1950 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Prints by Hiroshige, 1951-1953 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Program 1951/1952, 1949-1951 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Programs, 1950-1951 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Programs: Friday Evening/Sunday Afternoon, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Programs: General, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Programs: General, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Programs: Nancy Durett, Violin Recital, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Promenade Concerts: Trust Fund Orchestra, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Promotion, 1950-1958, folder 1 of 2 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Promotion, 1950-1958, folder 2 of 2 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Promotion 1956/57 Season, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Prospects, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Public Relations: "Report of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts" by Earl Newsom and Company, 1958-1970 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Publications 1945-1946: Lists, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Publications, 1955-1956 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Publications, 1969-1972 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Publications: New, 1949-1956 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Publications: Recipients of Bound Volumes, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Publications of Virginia Museum, 1938-1950 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Publications of Virginia Museum, 1938-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 78)
- Publications of Virginia Museum, 1941-1948 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Publicity: 18th Biennial Exhibition Virginia Artists, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Publicity: 25th Anniversary Fund, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Publicity: 25th Birthday - Chapter Invitations, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Publicity: 25th Birthday Exhibition - Yu Wine Vessel 1960 November 11, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Publicity: 25th Birthday Year - "Museum President says 1961 will be greatest year" 1960 September 1, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Publicity: 5th College Drama Festival - Letter to Trustees, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Publicity: Abrams, Humphreys, Carter 1960 October 2, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Publicity: Affiliate Dinners, 1960 9 September, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Publicity: Affiliate Dinners in Museum 1960 September 15, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Publicity: Affiliates - Humelsine 1960 September 29, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Publicity: American Craftsman's Exhibition, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Publicity: American Sculpture Today - Photographs, Undated (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Publicity: April and May 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - Charlottesville Release, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - Enclosure Picture, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - General Release to Major City Dailies, UP and AP, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - Mailing Cover Letter, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - Norfolk Release, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - Roanoke Releases, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - Statewide Releases, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - to Affiliates, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- Publicity: Arts in Virginia - Williamsburg Release, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- Publicity: Birthday Events, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 31)
- Publicity: Birthday Party - Awards 1961 February 24, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 32)
- Publicity: Built in USA, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 33)
- Publicity: Bulletin - September, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 34)
- Publicity: Bulletin - September, 1955 [1] (Box 50, Folder 35)
- Publicity: Bulletin - September 1955 [2] (Box 50, Folder 36)
- Publicity: Bulletins, 1952-1959 (Box 50, Folder 37)
- Publicity: Bulletins, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 38)
- Publicity: Bus Tours to Carousel, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 39)
- Publicity: Carousel, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 40)
- Publicity: Carousel 1960 October 19, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 41)
- Publicity: Carousel - Buses 1960 November 3, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 42)
- Publicity: Certificate Winners - Virginia Artists, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 43)
- Publicity: Chamber Music 1960 October 11, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 44)
- Publicity: Chamber Music Society, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 45)
- Publicity: Chapter Plans, Undated (Box 50, Folder 46)
- Publicity: Chapter Releases, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 47)
- Publicity: Christmas Cards - Photographs, Undated (Box 50, Folder 48)
- Publicity: Cigar Store Indians - Photographs, Undated (Box 50, Folder 49)
- Publicity: College Dance Festival 1960 December 2, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 50)
- Publicity: College Drama Festival, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 51)
- Publicity: College Drama Festival - Film, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 52)
- Publicity: College Drama Festival - Photographs, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 53)
- Publicity: College Drama Festival - to the Schools, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 54)
- Publicity: Core Collection, 1952-1953 (Box 50, Folder 55)
- Publicity: Correspondence, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 56)
- Publicity: Current and Active, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 57)
- Publicity: Dance Society, Undated (Box 50, Folder 58)
- Publicity: Dance Society - Photographs, Undated (Box 50, Folder 59)
- Publicity: Design for the Theater, 1952-1953 (Box 50, Folder 60)